is it true are you going to marry Zaki's girl are you serious yeah I just got off the phone
with him and he went on and on and on about setting a wedding day for the two of you
although I guess he did sound a little slashed I'm assuming you and Santa are at least dating
no absolutely not ah well that's a bummer but you do have a girlfriend right no girlfriend
for that matter I don't even have a friend friend huh what'd you say by the way Kobito has a boyfriend
she's staying at his place again tonight what who the hell is he who's the bastard that made a move
on my angel I'm coming back home right now making that criminal pay relax I was kidding bye dad
Yo, guys, what's up?
Hey! Kobito's here! Awesome!
Go away!
You're so funny!
By any chance, do you want to go with me to the amusement park tomorrow?
No.
Are you sure about that? Check it out, I've got a pass to Yokoshima Wonderland.
Somebody from work gave my daddy some tickets.
Oh, and there's this!
There'll be limited edition stuff there, and I'll buy you snacks and a yummy hamburger, too.
Limited edition?
Hamburgers?
That does sound like fun.
There's no reason to be scared.
I'll be really gentle with you, and I promise we'll have fun.
So what do you say, little sister?
Good grief, meat. How pathetic can you get?
What do you think you're doing? Get back, stupid jerk!
Have you been to that park before, Yozara?
Yeah, I went on a field trip there when I was in the eighth grade.
I'm pretty sure I spent the entire time reading a book, though.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
I've actually been there before, but it was with my family.
And ever since then, I've wanted to go to an amusement park with some of my friends.
Yeah, I kind of have, too.
Okay, tomorrow we are all going to go to Yokoshima Wonderland together.
We are?
School's out, and we've got time to kill anyway, so why not?
Good point.
It's a weekday, so it probably won't be too crowded.
Rika's all about it.
Big brother, I shall accompany you as well.
Yay! I'm going to the amusement park!
I suppose I could entertain myself with a human pastime just this once.
All right, it's decided then.
Not so fast!
I only invited Kobito, not the entire freaking club!
What? This ticket admits six adults, doesn't it?
We're helping you make sure it doesn't go to waste.
Hold on.
It's for adults, not kids?
Hooray! Hooray!
Wait, does this mean I can't go now?
Because I'm a little girl?
You're too young for the ticket.
I guess I forget sometimes that I'm just a little girl.
Don't worry. I'm used to it.
You all go and have a great time.
No, I guess I can shell out enough to buy a kid's ticket.
You can still go.
Do you really mean it?
You're such a good person!
Thank you so much, Senna.
Thank you, thank you!
Hey, I'm Senna.
What is it?
Was it just me, or did you notice something kind of off about your dad yesterday, too?
I don't know.
Although, now that you mention it, he got all happy and started drinking after giving me those tickets to the park,
which I guess was a little random.
You know why?
No clue.
All I could think about was inviting Kobito to go with me, so I wasn't really paying attention.
Naturally.
It was probably just a bunch of drunken rambling anyway.
Tomorrow is going to be awesome, isn't it, Kobito?
No!
You are so adorbs!
This place is amazing!
We finally made it to the fabled amusement park!
I wonder if this is Senna's first time here, too.
So which ride do you guys think we should go on first?
You guys?
This one!
The Black Dragon!
What?
Are you crazy?
You seriously want to go straight to the Black Dragon?
I swore to myself I'd ride this.
For the record, I didn't stay up all night deciding whether or not to ride it like some people.
I just figured I should, since it's famous and everything.
Prepare yourself, Dragon of the Night.
The Black Dragon.
That title seems fitting for those who are real men.
Me too!
Come on!
Let's go!
Let's go ride it!
Fine, but don't come crying to me later.
Let's go!
So far, this isn't all that bad.
From up here, all the common folk on the ground look like ants.
What's the problem, Dark Dragon?
Is this really all you have for me?
How sad.
Rika's getting stimulated by these vibrations,
and they're definitely making her all hot and bothered, as they say.
Crap.
I don't think I like how high we are.
Oh, yes.
Bring it on.
Take me, Black Dragon.
Take me to the far reaches of time and space, and, um...
Uh...
I want to get off now, please?
There is something so wrong with whoever thought of this lame ride.
I bet it was a freak pervert.
You're nothing but a toy!
You're lying to me again, you poopy, Yotara!
If I die, it's your fault!
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Seriously, Doctor, I don't mind me now!
Yes, here it comes.
Ah!
We're all going to die!
We're all going to win!
We're going to win!
Hells yeah.
OwOoOoOoOoOoOoOOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOnooOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoHoOoOoOoOoOOoOoOoTheOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOoOO
I'll kill you, please!
You better help me!
Help me! Help me!
Therefore in the void there are no one.
You better ejaculate faster than the speed of light
because I'm trying to catch you!
What the hell are you talking about?!
So, what did you guys think?
That was super duper fun!
I'm not sure.
Rika's head hurts so bad.
What happened? Rika can't remember anything.
Ladies and gentlemen, may I have your attention, please?
The official Full Metal Necromancer skit
will be performing on the main stage at 10.45.
We hope to see you all there shortly.
Once again, that's 10.45 on the main stage.
Hoobadoo!
Do you want me to go with you?
Let's go now so we can get good seats!
Hey! Wait for me!
Coobadoo, I almost forgot to tell you I just bought the entire Full Metal Necromancer series on Blu-ray.
And I don't think I ever told you that I'm actually a huge fan of the show, too.
Which one is your favorite character?
I like that girl, Mel.
She's from the second season and not a very big character.
But still, I think she's got so many dimensions, you know?
It's Meryl.
Huh?
Meryl.
From Season 2, Episode 8.
The Phoenix Tamer.
Emerod Mariel Von Liveracea Otori's nickname is Meryl.
It's not Mel.
Oh!
Yeah, you're right.
That's who I meant.
And she came back, also appearing in Episode 5 of Season 3.
Oh, I haven't gotten quite that far yet.
Senna, my sister is a ridiculous fanatic when it comes to this show, so if you don't know your stuff, acting like you do will just piss her off.
I don't get it.
Man, I wish real-life conversations came with personalized options and multiple save points.
Welcome, boys and girls.
Thank you so much for coming to our show.
Lucky for us, a really cool friend came here today just to hang out with you guys.
Who?
She's from Full Metal Necromancer.
Now give it up for Guernica!
Yeah!
So, are you ready to meet her?
Let's all say her name together, okay?
Guernica!
Huh?
My name is Astaroth.
Guernica's going to be a little late thanks to the trap I set for her.
In the meantime, I'm taking you hostage.
Oh, no! Someone help me!
I don't suppose any of you minuscule kids would want to join us on the stage and be my hostage as well.
There's a free gift for anyone brave enough to let me take them hostage, so...
Sounds like a pretty sweet deal to me.
Me?
I'll do it! I'll be the best hostage ever! Pick me!
Senna, put your hand down, please.
Trust me, you don't have to worry about anything, Kobito. I'm so getting that gift for you.
Are you serious?
Yeah, like I care about some gift from this stupid show.
Thank you, but we'd like to ask the mothers in the crowd to let their kids go first.
Huh? Wait, who's a mother?
Why would I take a mother hostage when I can have one of her kids?
What in the heck are they talking about?
If I had to make a guess, I'd say they're assuming you're Kobito's mother.
But why would they think something's so obviously not true? And besides, that would mean that they probably think that you're her father, which would make you my husband. That's so messed up.
It's totally messed up. You got that right.
What do you mean by that?!
Talk about rude.
Anyone!
Hey, little girl. You wanna volunteer?
Be a great time, I swear!
You sure, Kobito?
Thanks. Watch your step, okay?
That's so awesome. You got the director's autograph. Good thing Senna spoke up. Because otherwise, I doubt they would have asked you to volunteer.
Uh, yeah. Thanks. I, uh, thank you, Senna.
Oh, Kobito!
I'll never get over how cute she is when she acts shy and runs away from me!
I wanna thank you, too, Senna. That was cool of you.
Well, it isn't like I did it for you or anything. This whole day was for Kobito, so...
And what was up with those awful actors? Us? Married? I mean, whatever.
We're not even a couple. We need to be that first. And we aren't.
What are you saying?
Nothing, so just shut up!
So, what have you guys been doing so far?
I just sat on a bench and read my book.
Rika went on the merry-go-round ten times in a row!
I ate a hot dog and popcorn and crepe and, let's see, what else did I have?
Oh, one of those-
You bought all that for her? Why? You didn't have to.
Nonsense. It was no trouble. I enjoyed looking after your sister. It was an honor.
Here you go, honey.
Yay! I love curry! It looks like two!
Your life depends on you not finishing that sentence.
Curry tastes really yummy!
Good.
I don't let her.
What do you guys want to do after we finish eating?
Let me go back and ride the black dragon again!
I think we've all had enough of the black dragon today. Right?
Wrong. I mean, I'm totally down to hit up that rollercoaster again. It was a blast.
But if you guys are just too scared to go, I completely understand.
Don't go playing all tough meat. You thought for sure you were gonna die.
Oh? Says the girl who was screaming for help the entire time?
Shut up. I was so not.
Yeah, that's right. Your pathetic screams are perfectly preserved in my mind.
At least I wasn't the one who was crying.
And I happen to know you peed in your pants a little.
How did you know that?
Are you kidding? You really did?
Of course not. Don't be stupid.
That lame coaster didn't scare me at all.
Unlike you and your panic cries for help.
Fine. Then why don't you prove it to us by going another round?
Cool. Let's do it.
But I'm not going unless you go with me.
My camera will prove you can't ride that thing without screaming your nasty head off.
Hold on. Since when do you have a camera?
Hmm. Hidden and ready since always.
Who are you hiding it from?
No one. It doesn't matter.
Let's go on this one next.
Don't listen to her big brother.
Rika wants to go here.
We're so high right now.
Those humans look like ants.
That thing's no joke. I've never been on a coaster that intense before.
Speaking of, I wonder how Yozara and Senna are doing.
It's been a really long time since we split up.
Do you think we should go find out where they are?
Big brother.
Hmm?
The girls are over there.
My head hurts.
I feel sick.
Whoa. What happened to you two?
Eight times.
Black dragon.
You rode the black dragon eight times.
Yozara wouldn't admit that she lost to me big time.
Meat wouldn't hurry up and just die big time.
Interesting.
Which one of you is the final winner?
Unfortunately, this battle's not over.
It's time to get the ninth round started.
Are you about ready?
Come on, guys.
You don't have to do this anymore.
Nothing wrong with calling it a tie.
Not happening.
Over my dead body.
She'll never beat me.
I won't allow.
Oh!
It's settled.
Meet in the waiting room at four.
Uh-huh.
Maria, why are you coming to the men's side?
Because I don't want to go with the girls because they smell like vomit and that's gross.
Fair enough.
I guess I can't fault you for that.
Yay!
I'm gonna take a bath with Big Brother!
Big Brother, I shall wash your back for you.
No, thank you.
I'm fine.
I can do it myself.
Of course.
As you wish.
I can see that I am completely useless to you.
In that case, I must...
Okay, fine.
You can wash it.
Please wash my back, Yukimura.
As you wish.
I will not let you down.
Come on.
Get it together, Kodaka.
Don't forget this guy is a dude.
Huh.
Huh?
So this must be what a weenie looks like.
Bad girl, give me that towel.
Yeah, okay.
But I don't understand why you have that weird thing.
What do you mean by weird?
It's perfectly normal.
All guys have these.
Oh.
Okay.
Well, how come Yukimura doesn't have one then?
Huh?
Yukimura is a boy without a weenie.
That makes him weird.
It's only because I haven't matured enough yet.
Huh?
Does that mean you'll grow one when you get older?
Yes.
I shall work hard to be a full-fledged man like my mentor, Big Brother.
I hope you get to get one soon.
Ugh!
You're not making sense!
Hmm.
Ugh!
What the?
He doesn't have one.
Forgive me.
I'm just easily embarrassed.
I feel so much better.
Of course a guy this cute isn't actually a guy.
Where do you want to go now?
Over there!
Well, Rika did not see that one coming.
Hmm.
Excuse Rika for a minute.
Ugh.
Hold on!
Rika?
Ugh!
It is true!
There's no doubt about it, Kodaka!
Yuki Mura's been a girl this whole time!
That's exactly what I just told you.
Oh!
Rika's used to checking things out personally for science.
Good.
I'm glad you're convinced.
Can you make Yuki Mura believe it too?
I didn't have much luck with that.
Weird stuff is all you ever want Rika for.
Ugh.
Fine.
Yuki Mura, dude, come with me please.
You don't have a yaoi hole.
Really?
Nope.
Sorry, girl.
People have said that before, but I thought I would get one and be a boy eventually.
Kodaka, I have bad news.
I'm afraid I'm not a true powerful man.
That's probably because you're not even a man to begin with.
No, wait!
Don't cry!
Please stop that!
I deeply apologize.
Hey, can you at least tell me what made you think you were really a boy all this time?
Just family circumstances.
Uh-huh.
Wait!
That's the end of the explanation?
It is.
I'm shocked that no one figured this out before.
Actually, a few people have noticed and pointed it out to her previously, but she decided not to listen to them.
Right.
Of course.
I'm glad Rika managed to bring her around.
Kodaka.
Hmm?
Do I still get to be your little brother?
I'm not a boy, but I can't just stop looking up to you.
You're still my little bro.
It's gonna take a lot more than you being a girl to change that.
Good.
That's such a relief.
Thank you so much.
I'll always remain your devoted servant.
Jeez, Kodaka.
Why are you blushing?
How crazy is this?
Yukimura is suddenly looking totally adorable to me.
I mean, talk about Moe.
Moe?
Yeah, the pretty little maid type.
Damn it.
How could I be looking up to you?
You're still my little bro.
It's gonna take a lot more than you being a girl to change that.
Good.
That's such a relief.
Thank you so much.
Damn it.
How could I be so completely blind?
All this time I thought he was just strange.
Hey guys, what's the matter with Yozara?
She's so pretty and sweet and super submissive.
Perfectly willing to be his personal slave.
Give me a break.
I can't take it.
I have the worst luck.
Why does everything always have to suck so hard?
They all look so cute.
When they're sleeping they almost remind me of normal girls.
Big brother.
What I'm wondering, Tim?
You can't take that too long.
Okay.
Friday night.
Okay, so weird.
Here we are some Dad showle.
Big brother out there on the bed.
Week's so pretty beauty.
Yes.
All of our food at that time goes forth.
All this tomorrow goes in.
Here you can never forget.
Alright, and again I saw each other four,
On the way…
I'm still so shocked, I never imagined I was actually a girl.
It's not that uncommon for a pretty boy character to turn out to be a girl,
but this is the first time Rika's seen it in third person.
Yeah, well, change isn't always that awesome, okay?
Oh, my apologies, sir.
Next time, that kind of play is not allowed.
And my worldview is disturbed when you are around.
Hey, Rika wonders what you they're talking about.
It's you, Rika.
It was a spoiler alert!
Thank you.